[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All but one of the following are true types of bears. Which is the odd one?", "correct_answer": "Moon bear", "incorrect_answers": ["Brown bear", "Black bear", "Sun bear"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what state is there a town called Jupiter?", "correct_answer": "Florida", "incorrect_answers": ["Georgia", "Alaska", "Alabama"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A bat is featured on the coat of arms of this Spanish city.", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Palma de Mallorca", "Fraga", "Valencia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sharks have no bones.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The planet Mars is named after which of the following?", "correct_answer": "Roman God of War", "incorrect_answers": ["A Candy Bar", "Roman God of Peace", "Greek God of the Sea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the odd one of the four writers?", "correct_answer": "Charles Dickens", "incorrect_answers": ["Thomas More", "Edmund Spenser", "Christopher Marlowe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these lists does NOT contain only primary Batman villains?", "correct_answer": "Catwoman, The Joker, Melody, Two-Face, Mr. Freeze", "incorrect_answers": ["Mr. Freeze, The Joker, Clayface, Bane, Scarecrow", "Poison Ivy, Bane, The Joker, The Riddler, Ventriloquist", "Penguin, Poison Ivy, Mad Hatter, Ras Al Ghul, Clayface"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He won the 2000 Nobel Peace Prize for his work promoting peace and democracy.", "correct_answer": "Kim Dae Jung", "incorrect_answers": ["Jo El Karl", "Leon Jouhaux", "James Jarrod"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The term \u2018petrodollar\u2019, a dollar earned by a country through the sale of oil, was invented in 1973 by this Egyptian-born American professor and economist.", "correct_answer": "Ibrahim Oweiss", "incorrect_answers": ["M. King Hubert", "Ronald R. Cooke", "Matthew R. Simmons"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is the surface temperature of the Sun?", "correct_answer": "9950 Degrees Fahrenheit", "incorrect_answers": ["11450 Degrees Fahrenheit", "7450 Degrees Fahrenheit", "2350 Degrees Fahrenheit"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which explorer was the first to reach the South Pole?", "correct_answer": "Roald Amundsen", "incorrect_answers": ["Richard Byrd", "Sir Robert Falcon Scott", "Sir Ernest Henry Shackleton"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Rowan Atkinsons passion for these objects caused him to amass an impressive collection.", "correct_answer": "Cars", "incorrect_answers": ["Stamps", "Bicycles", "Coins"]}]